i got another one okay um i travel a lot and especially after covid we got to see that a lot
of folks is nasty uh they're not washing hands all right uh they're just doing a lot of things
that are really calling into question the need for us to have some sort of a hygiene task force
so we would call this the so fresh and so clean act and it would divert funding uh to a a tsa
type task force that would be called uh the wtf the wash rag task force um and this would be in place
to i thought you were going somewhere else well you know the reality is is we we need folks to
not feel so comfortable about walking into airplane bathrooms barefoot you know and if they knew that
they would get a citation i i feel like this would be really helpful for me or at least we would get
less people sharing their weird stuff online yes like i just don't understand why people are like
i don't take showers i don't wash myself after i use the bathroom like and they're on podcasts yes we
should actually have another task force to just stop people from having podcasts yeah because that's
another problem that i think is plaguing america
that's another problem that i think is plaguing america